Guide to the Duke University Union Records, 1954-ongoing UA.09.13.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Records1954-ongoing, 54 boxes
  - Galleries: Michael Dillon, March 12-April 15, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Chas Ray Krider, March 12-April 15, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Lori Davis, May 10-September 23, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Andrew and Denice Janssen, May 11-July 1, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Diane Rodwell, July 1-August 17, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Interaction Committee: General, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: General, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Jazz, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Chance Concert, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: R.E.M. Concert, October 3-4, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: R.E.M. Contract and Rider, October 3-4, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Let's Active, October 10, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Al Jarreau, October 10, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Love and Rockets, November 16, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Love and Rockets, Ticket Sales and Distribution, November 16, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Love and Rockets, Contracts, November 16, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Bo Deans, December 4, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Echo and the Bunnymen, February 20, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Echo and the Bunnymen, Tickets, February 20, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Mike Cross, April 15, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Mike Cross, Tickets 15-Apr-88 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Centerfest 1987, Durham Arts Council, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Major Attractions: Trouble Funk, Springfest, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Performing Arts: General, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Performing Arts: Advertising, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Performing Arts: BSA/Gambia National Dance, March 1, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Performing Arts: Candide, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Performing Arts: The Last Flapper [cancelled], 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Performing Arts: Steven Wright, December 2, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Performing Arts: Showcase, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Performing Arts: Give 'Em Hell Harry, April 16, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Broadway at Duke: Brochure, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Broadway at Duke: Playbill, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Broadway at Duke: Tickets, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Broadway at Duke: The Glass Menagerie, October 4, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Broadway at Duke: I'm Not Rappaport, February 10, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Performing Arts: World Saxophone Quartet, November 15, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Programming for University Bars: Barrence Whitfield and the Savages, September 16, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Programming for University Bars: Fetchin' Bones, October 10, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Programming for University Bars: Boweevils, November 5, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Programming for University Bars: Connells, November 24, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Programming for University Bars: Alex Chilton, December 10, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Programming for University Bars: Cosponsorships, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Programming for University Bars: Connells [Springfest], April 8, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Programming for University Bars: Go To Blazes, April 14, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Publicity Brochure, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Miscellaneous PR and Publicity Materials, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Summer Enrichment Program, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Special Events, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Special Events: Homecoming - Embers, October 31, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Special Events: Rocky Horror, October 31, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Special Events: Club Coca-Cola, November 6, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Special Events: Club Coca-Cola Ticket Sales, November 6, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Special Events: Tree Lighting, December 1, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Special Events: Springfest, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Special Events: Fashion Symposium, April 12, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Duke University Union Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Graduate Survey, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Surveys and Analysis, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Senator Sanford/Tom Walker, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - New Computer, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Surveys and Analysis, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Programming Council, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Drama/Student Groups, mostly late 1980s (Box 27)
  - Executive Board, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Programming for University Bars, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Finance, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Image of Black in Western Art, October 16-November 14, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Proposed Budgets, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Child Care, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - University Union Board, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - National Association of Black Students for Educational Advancement, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Galleries Committee: General Correspondence, Spring 1988 (Box 27)
  - Facilities Committee: Report to Board, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Facilities Committee: General Records, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Rolls and Constitution, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Retreat Agenda, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Summer Enrichment Program, June 19-25, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Summer Programming, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Chapel Reception, July 24, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Programming Council: Meeting, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - SAC Week [Student Activism], 1988 (Box 28)
  - Pink Flamingos, undated (Box 28)
  - Freewater/Cable 13/Perkins: "The Spider's Web", 1987-1988 (Box 28)
  - Summer Programming, 1987 (Box 28)
  - Cable 13: General, 1987-1988 (Box 28)
  - Finance: Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Fall Schedules [various committees], 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - VP Programming: General, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Interaction Committee: Metrosport Party, October 1, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Cosponsorships: Art Events, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Yearlook, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Cable 13: General, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Cable 13: Summer Schedule 1988 (Box 28)
  - Last Lecture Series, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Pedro San Juan [cancelled], 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Flowers Gallery Schedule, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Schedule, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Angelico Cruz, August 18-September 30, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Robert Amberg, August 19-September 23, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Connie Schwab, September 24-October 29, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: David Benson, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Donna Gregory, October 2-28, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Benini, October 30-December 15, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Bragtown School, December, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Laura Paresky, January 8-February 6, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Maureen Banker, January 9-February 10, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Rita Fitzpatrick, February 4-26, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Sherman Fleming, February 7-March 3, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Traudi Thornton, February 9-April 4, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Cathryn Griffin, February 11-March 19, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Kristine Stiles [cancelled], February 16-March 18, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Larry Dew, March 4-20, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Lance Blum, March 19-April 14, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Eric Green, March 20-April 16, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Econ Streetman, April 3-30, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Linda Nisselson, April 15-May 19, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Interior/Exterior, April 18. 1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: George Buchanan, May 19-July 28, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries: Nili Aharoni, May 25-July 6, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Interaction Committee: General, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Interaction: Marilyn Lowen [speaker], April 5, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Interaction: Talent Show, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Major Attractions: Kaleidoscope - Laser Show, September 22, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Major Attractions: Bruce Hornsby, September 30, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Major Attractions: Bruce Hornsby Tickets, September 30, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Major Attractions: UB40, October 4, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Major Attractions: Windham Hall, November 15, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Major Attractions: Jerry Seinfeld, December 3, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Calendar, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Programming Council Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Policy Revisions, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Minutes [various committees], 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - ASDU, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Vice President Griffith, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Finance, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Budgetary Information, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Budgets, 1988-1990 (Box 28)
  - Constitutional Amendments, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Executive Board, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Programming Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Minorities Party, circa 1980s (Box 28)
  - Student Activities Council, circa 1980s (Box 28)
  - Imani, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Talent Show, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Facilities Committee: Financial Handbook, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Facilities Committee: Bryan Center Space, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Wenhai Ma, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Janssen, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Robert Amberg, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Irving Sandler, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Lori Davis, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Angelico Cruz, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Pedro San Juan, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Bragtown 6th Grade Center, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Dianne T. Rodwell, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Artists - Information, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Survey, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: New York City, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Jack Tilton, NYC, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Flyers, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: General Correspondence, late-1980s (Box 28)
  - Galleries Committee: Michel DeManche, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - GPSC, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Summer Enrichment, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Cable 13, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Yearlook: Renegotiation, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Cable 13: SALAP, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Tax Agreement Forms: Oktoberfest, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Minutes [various committees], 1986-1987 (Box 29)
  - Finance: Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Finance: Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Cable Report, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Portable Equipment, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Recruitment, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Financial Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Member Lists, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Organization/Assignments, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Programming Meeting, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Sign-ups and Assignments, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Student-Run Organizations Report, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Student-Run Organization Problem, S.O.S. Meeting, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Special Projects, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: General, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Broadcast Schedules, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Athletic Department, Van Renovations, June 29, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Purchases, Van and Studio, Summer 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Crossword Contest, February 28, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: General Information, Yearlook, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Technical, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Minutes, Space and Facilities Meeting between Academic and Extracurricular Sectors, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Planned Projects, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Cable Report, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Outside Programming Office, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Bryan Center Move, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Grants, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: CSN Contract, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Executive Committee Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Misc/General, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Cable System (Tom Houston), 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Rock World Contract, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: SWAN (Emergency Information System), 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Chronology of Events, Fall 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Reception, September 9, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: UJB Video, October 3, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Executive Committee Meetings, November 15, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Nick Morris Reply (equipment use), November 20, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: David Ball Letter, November 24, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Survey, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Show Proposals, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Dr. David Ball Memoranda, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Richard A. White's Memo to Nick Morris, December 1, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Dean's Advisory Council for the Arts, December 7, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Meetings Regarding Space and Facilities, January 13, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Reagan Visit, February 2, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: "A Walk in the Woods" Commercial, February 3-6, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: CSN - Presidential Debates, February 18, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Dr. H. Keith H. Brodie Memo, April 6, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: University Governance Committee Report, April 12, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Letters to Members of the Task Force, May 12, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Durham Cablevision, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Articles, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Engineering Memo, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Nightly News, 1976-1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Miscellaneous Records, 1987-1989 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Films, 1987-1989 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Photos, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Engineering Memo, September 23, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Instructional Memo, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Publicity/Advertising, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Survey Example, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: "Community TV Comes of Age," Deban Dawson, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Purchase and Repair, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Programming, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: CSN - Sex on Campus, September 30, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: CSN - American Foreign Policy, October 2, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Nicholas B. Morris Memorandum, December 22, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, etc., 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, etc., 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Retreat: Winter 1988 (Box 29)
  - Programming: Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, etc., 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Special Events: Tree Lighting, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Durham Cablevision, 1983; 1989 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13, Summer 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Outline/Checklist for Camera Usage, September 1, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Alumni Letter, 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Proposals, 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Duke Music Cooperative, 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: CSN, 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: National Association of Collegiate Broadcasters, 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Retreat: Fall 1988 (Box 29)
  - Galleries: Meetings, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Galleries: Calendars, 1989-1991 (Box 29)
  - Art Events, 1988-1993 (Box 29)
  - Yearlook, circa 1989 (Box 29)
  - Performing Arts, 1989-1990 (Box 29)
  - SALAP [Student Affairs Leadership Assistance Program], Summer 1989 (Box 29)
  - Finance: Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Internship Directory 1989 (Box 29)
  - Cable 13: Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Galleries: Guest Register, Brown Gallery, July-September, 1988 (Box 46)
  - Galleries: Guest Register, Connie Rubino Schwab, September-October, 1988 (Box 46)
  - Galleries: Guest Register, Donna Gregory, October 1, 1988 (Box 46)
  - Galleries: Guest Register, various exhibits, 1988 (Box 46)
  - Broadway at Duke: Brochure, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Broadway at Duke: General, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Broadway at Duke: Tickets, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Broadway at Duke: Advertising, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Broadway at Duke: Playbill, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Broadway at Duke: Jake's Women, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Broadway at Duke: Forbidden Broadway, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Broadway at Duke: Drood, October 11, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Broadway at Duke: Nunsense, October 27, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Broadway at Duke: Little Shop of Horrors, November 10, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Broadway at Duke: 1,000 Airplanes on the Roof, February 24, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Broadway at Duke: Showcase '89, February 25, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Broadway at Duke: A View From the Bridge, March 5, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Broadway at Duke: Hudson Vagabond Puppets, March 28, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Programming for University Bars: Waxing Poetics, September 2, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Programming for University Bars: Living Colour, October 8, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Programmng for University Bars: Barrence Whitfield and the Savages, February 22, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, October 7, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Special Events: Homecoming, October 21, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Special Events: Rocky Horror [cancelled - rain], October 31, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Special Events: Reebok, November 18, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Special Events: Tree Lighting, November 29, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Special Events: Club Coca Cola [cancelled], March 3, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Special Events: Charles Zucker, March 29, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Special Events: Installation of Officers, April 4, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Special Events: Springfest, April 14, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Special Events: Springfest, Dreams So Real, April 14, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Special Events: Springfest, Guadalcanal Diary, April 14, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Tax Agreement Forms: Springfest, 1989 (Box 30)
  - DUU Alumni, circa 1988 (Box 30)
  - Union Annual Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Cable 13: Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Facilities Committee: Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Finance Committee: Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Major Speakers, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Major Attractions, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Galleries: Schedule, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Special Events, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Springfest, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Union Representative, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Programming Council: Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - ASDU Office Space Application, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Flowers Gallery, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - ASDU, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Heart Strings/Haring, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Retreat Fall, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Retreat Spring, 1990 (Box 30)
  - Proposals, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - New Student Gallery, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Law School Referendum, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Long Range Planning, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Search Committee (Financial Advisor), 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Young Trustee, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Brodie Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Facilities, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Theaters Facilities Users, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Symposium, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Institute of the Arts, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Programming Information, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - GPSC, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Union Meetings, etc., 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Black on White, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - University Union Board, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Agendas, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Event Evaluation, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Unity Day, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Cable 13, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Richard Whitted Institute, Summer 1989 (Box 30)
  - Yearlook, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Union Calendars, circa 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Student Activities, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Concerts, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Conference Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Share Your Christmas, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Down Under, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Finance: Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - University Union Board Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 31)
  - Executive Committe Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 31)
  - Visual Arts: Rita Fitzpatrick, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Visual Arts: Press Releases, 1988-1989 (Box 31)
  - Visual Arts: Polly Palumbo, 1988-1989 (Box 31)
  - Programming: Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 31)
  - Holiday Workshop, 1988-1989 (Box 31)
  - University Union Board Miscellany, 1987-1989 (Box 31)
  - S.A.L.A.P., 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Random Info, VPA, Fall 1989 (Box 31)
  - Black Student Alliance, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Budgets, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Budget, 1989 (Box 31)
  - DUU General Records, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Referendum, 1990 (Box 31)
  - Volunteer Service Center, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Vice President Griffith, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Newsletter, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Policies, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Programming Council Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 31)
  - IR, Speed Orders, etc., 1980s (Box 31)
  - Long Range Planning, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Retreats thru late 1980s: General Information, late 1980s (Box 31)
  - Retreats: Leadership Exercises, late 1980s (Box 31)
  - Facilities Committee: Office Space Applications, 1989-1993 (Box 31)
  - Facilities Committee: Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Constitutions, 1988-1990 (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Finance Committee: Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Financial Handbook, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Facilities Committee: Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Finance Committee: Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Financial Handbook, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Facilities Committee: Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Broadway at Duke: General, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Broadway at Duke: Tickets, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Broadway at Duke: Brochure, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Broadway at Duke: Advertising, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Duke Union Grand Reopening, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Special Events: General, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Major Speakers: Cosponsorships, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Major Speakers: Alice Walker, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Major Speakers: Nancy Hanks, Symposium on the Arts, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Major Speakers: Jimmy Carter, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Last Lecture Series, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Galleries Committee: Laurie Anderson, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Programming for University Bars: Cosponsorships, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Programming for University Bars: Prospects, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Performing Arts Committee: General Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Unity, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Connells (Habitat Benefit), 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Galleries: Geri Camarda, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Galleries: Rita Schwab, 1989-1990 (Box 31)
  - Galleries: D. Bryan Carey, III, August 17-September 14, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Galleries: Syndi Moser, August 26-September 24, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Galleries: Doug Deneen, September 15-October 24, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Major Attractions: The Cure, September 20, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Major Attractions: Fine Young Cannibals, September 27, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Galleries: Donna Gregory, October 2-28, 1988 (Box 31)
  - Galleries: Peter Dean, October 5-November 8, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Galleries: Connie Schwab, October 1988 (Box 31)
  - Oktoberfest, October 6, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Oktoberfest: Seven Simons/Royal Crescent Mob, October 6, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Major Speakers: Studs Terkel, October 10, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Broadway at Duke: "Working", October 11, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Georgia Sea Island Singers, October 19, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Galleries: Lorraine Benini, October 20-December 15, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Major Speakers: Errol Morris, October 20, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Galleries: Marthanna Yater, October 25-November 20, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, October 28-29, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Galleries: David Benson, October 29-December 2, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Major Speakers: Congressman Bill Gray, October 30, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Rocky Horror Picture Show, October 31, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Major Speakers: Father Stallings, November 2, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Major Attractions: Bob Dylan, November 8, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Galleries: Danielle Epstein, November 9-December 2, 1989 (Box 31)